## **YANIV WEINSHTEIN**

Full-Stack Developer

Email Address Phone Number GitHub Portfolio LinkedIn Yanivwein22@gmail.com 0544718317 YanivWein24 Yaniv-Weinshtein Yaniv-Weinshtein

Full-stack developer with **1 year of professional experience** building web applications using React and Node.js. With a practical engineering degree in electronics, and a great passion for technology and innovation. Enjoys building web apps, with a tendency towards the front-end, and finding new documentations to explore!

#### **Experienced with the following libraries and technologies:**

Front-End: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Next.js, Redux, Context, React-Query, Axios, PWA,

Formik, I18Next, Styled components, Material-UI, Recharts, SCSS, CSS, HTML

Back-End: Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Prisma, Socket-IO, JWT, Passport.js, Oauth2.0, Nodemailer

**Misc:** Jest, Es-Lint, Git, Github-Actions, Circle-CI, Jira, Postman, Linux, Python

#### **Work experience**

#### Feb 2023 - Present: Socialo | Full Stack Developer (Link)

React, Node.js, MongoDB, Oauth, TypeScript, Context, React-Query, Formik, Styled-Components, Material-UI, I18N Building an AI-based B2B SaaS digital-marketing platform for businesses and marketing agencies. Leading product development from planning to production. Working end-to-end, writing clean, reusable, and typesafe code, managing integrations (AI models, Social networks, Analytics, etc.), building CI/CD pipelines, working with SCRUM methodology.

## Oct 2023 - Present: Fluffy Finder | Front End Developer | Volunteering (Link)

React, TypeScript, Context, Material-UI, AuthO, SWR, PWA

Joining the frontend team to continue a Work-In-Progress centralized system for reporting lost/found pets that use AI and algorithms to match between reports. Improving and refactoring the existing user interface, adding new features, integrating with the backend API and analytics providers, working alongside other development teams, designers, QA and a product manager.

# Oct 2022 - Jan 2023: eBigay | Front-End Developer | Volunteering (<u>Link</u>) React, TypeScript, PWA, Context, React-Query, Formik, Styled-Components, Material-UI

Working in the frontend team for a marketplace web app that connects donors with those in need. Developing responsive and user-friendly UI from scratch, according to the given design in Figma. Consuming the server API and collaborating with the back-end team. Working with SCRUM methodology.

### **Projects**

## - Similarity API: Next.js, TypeScript, Next-Auth, Prisma, Open-AI, Redis, TailwindCSS

A Full-Stack Next.js project, containing a rate-limited API in the back-end and a user dashboard with documentation in the front-end. The API receives 2 pieces of text, converts them to vectors, and returns a number between 0-1 representing the similarity of the 2 vectors.

Project GitHub Repository

- IP Address Tracker: React, TypeScript, Ipify-API, IP-Geolocation-API, Leaflet-Map

A tracking app that locates users by their IP address. Can locate any valid IPv4 address on the globe! Project GitHub Repository

#### **Education**

- The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp by Dr. Angela Yu, Udemy | 2022
- Practical Engineering In Electronics | Kziney Yam Acre | 2017-2019
- Major In Electronics Engineering 10 points | Kziney Yam Acre | 2014-2017